<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>
  <articles>
    <article>
      <folder>/images/article/economy/selected05/</folder>
      <title>The Captivating Aroma of Coffee Well Off the Beaten Track</title>
      <subtitle>
       Here you can taste Italian, hand-drip, or siphon coffee for around $100 NT; you can also try to make your own coffee.
      </subtitle>
      <author>By PEPE</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[<p>
                        Café Studio is a coffee house that I had been looking forward to visiting for some time and is now a secret haven of mine. When I actually visited, I found that it was a really cute shop. It's probably the smallest coffee house we'd ever been to! But the coffee and the friendly atmosphere there were amazing. We can go there several times a week and still find it interesting. We always have so much to talk about every time we go there. This is the enchantment of Café Studio.
                    </p>
                    <img src="../../images/article/economy/selected05/economy_bigpic.jpg" width="627" height="276" class="selected_pic" />


                    <p>
                        Café Studio's Chinese name is 'Dou Shi' (斗侍). This is pronounced exactly the same as the term 'dou shi' (斗室), which means 'small room'. The owners were advised by some feng sui expert that the word 'room' (室) would cause conflict, so they changed it to the word 'serve' (侍) with the same pronunciation in Chinese. Café Studio is on the 2nd floor next to the Ruen Kite Art Studio. The manager of Ruen Kite said that the old house was previously owned by an early Taiwanese poet, and the current landlord is a retired chemical engineering professor from Cheng Kung University. Most of his children live abroad and he has lived in Taoyuan for a long time. But he eventually came back to tidy up the old place. The manager of Ruen Kite adored the house but didn't know how to contact the landlord, so he wrote a letter, put it in a bottle and placed it in the garden. He never expected that the landlord would read the letter and be so moved that he would call and lease the property to Ruen Kite Art Studio.
                    </p>
                    <img src="../../images/article/economy/selected05/economy_pic1.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/economy/selected05/economy_pic2.jpg" />
                    <p>Café Studio's manager Squda and Ruen Kite's manager were classmates. They decided to rent the 2nd floor and open a coffee house. The 2nd floor is very tiny; it was originally a child's bedroom that the landlord added as an extension. What makes it unique are its numerous opening windows and rare fish-scale patterned glass. During the day, you can follow the drifting light and shadows of the sun; the blazing sunlight shines on different corners at different times throughout the day, but it never feels unpleasant. During the day or in the evening, you only have to sit by a window to gaze at the scenery of the alleyway outside or the clear sky above. Although the space is small, the fact that you can see the sky expands your field of view. 'Cramped' or 'poky' doesn't seem like the right word to describe Café Studio; we prefer to use 'relaxing' and 'comfortable' to define the atmosphere. Although there aren't many seats, Squda has kindly placed baskets under the seats for visitors to put their possessions in; I was comfortable even when I had arrived laden with bags of all shapes and sizes. I also unexpectedly found that the stairway handrails were wonderful to be used as chairs. The seat close to the counter has become my regular place.</p>
                    <img src="../../images/article/economy/selected05/economy_bigpic2.jpg" width="623" height="211" /><br />
                    <p>Here you can taste Italian, hand-drip, or siphon coffee for around $100 NT; you can also try to make your own coffee. Café Studio also provides a coffee bean roaster. You can take your raw beans along and roast. The rate is $250NT for 1.5 hours. It's OK if you don't have any raw beans; just add $150NT to choose your beans and roast them the way you like. Squda said that some day he will let customers set their own prices, so they can pay however much they think their cup of coffee is worth. He said self-mockingly that such a pricing strategy has never been tried before and will never be repeated. If it succeeds, he'll be the first; if it fails, no one else will make the same mistake!</p>
                    <p>Squda studied design. He designed the business cards and coffee bean packaging himself. Even the interior design was done by him. He also loves to read and buy books and has filled Café Studio with a treasure trove of interesting books that are well worth a read. Squda said that he has so many books at home that he can't bring them all at once, and that he'll just get another batch of books to share with customers after a while. These books aren't merely decorative; when there weren't any customers, Squda introduced each book for us. We sat drinking coffee and reading a book together. Coffee and the smell of books is an unforgettable memory of that day. I curiously asked Squda, "How many people can you accommodate in this small space?" He said, "Including customer's sitting on the 3rd floor stairway, the maximum is 8."</p>
                    <img src="../../images/article/economy/selected05/economy_pic3.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/economy/selected05/economy_pic4.jpg" />
                    <p>Hand-drip coffee can be served hot or cold. The hot version is served in a handmade transparent tea set and a snifter cup; the cold version is served in wine glasses. Transparent glasses show off the clear color of the coffee. This unique way of serving coffee in these special coffee cups is not strange at all at Café Studio, but actually feels quite comfortable. One of the coffee varieties that impressed me a lot was the "Bolivia Cenaproc", shortened to "Bolivia C"; we loved its maltose aroma, the sweetness of its puffed rice fragrance, and the sweetness of its light bake. I felt bad for Squda because we used so many cups and glasses, and it would take him a lot of time washing them all... :P</p>
                    <p>Squda, who had worked at many coffee shops, modestly refered to himself as the manager as opposed to the boss. Besides making coffee for the customers, he also enjoys interacting with them. Customers can determine how the space is used; if a customer wants to be alone, he'll let the customer use the space on the 2nd floor to spend some time alone, while he stays on the 1st floor to select beans. If a customer wants to try baking beans or making coffee, he'll gladly let them have a go. After drinking Squda's Italian coffee, hand-drip coffee and siphon coffee, I tried brewing espresso under his guidance. My first experience of baking beans ended in a fluster, but I had successfully baked my first bag of coffee. I tasted it before the beans had been aged. Although the taste wasn't perfect, I had gained a feeling of accomplishment from my new experiences. I'm deeply grateful to Squda for teaching me with such patience ^^.</p>
                    <p>Make sure you phone ahead before visiting. Sometimes there are a lot of customers and no more people can be accommodated. If you just show up, you might end up disappointed. So give Squda a call first and ask how full the place is to make sure you get the most out of your visit. I don't want to disturb the tranquility of the alleyway, so I won't disclose the address here. If you're interested, please call Squda. Café Studio doesn't have any signage. Even if you've made a reservation, the pale green door would not be open when you arrive. You have to call Squda again and he'll come down to let you in. ^^</p>

                </div>

                <div class="placeArea">
                    <div class="placeBG">
                        <span class="position-name">Café Studio</span>
                        <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
                            <tr>
                                <td class="item">Address：
            
                                </td>
                                <td>I won't disclose the address. Café Studio doesn't have much space, so you have to call and ask for the address before you visit. (Near University of Tainan)</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td>Telephone：</td>
                                <td>0988-162-298 / 
                                    10:00–20:00 (closed on Tuesdays)</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td>Transportation：</td>
                                <td>Take the train to Tainan Station, and walk for 15–20 minutes or take a taxi for 5 minutes.</td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                    </div>
                    <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>1</subjectid>
      <region>4</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/0?category=economy</link>
    </article>
    <article>
      <folder>/images/article/economy/selected02/</folder>
      <title>Viewing Plum Blossoms at Wusonglun</title>
      <subtitle>
        Pure, beautiful plum blossoms were brought to life by the blue skies. Gazing at plum blossoms is the ideal way to enjoy the winter sunshine on a chilly January day.
      </subtitle>
      <author>黑大王</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[
		<p><img title="Pselected0200034.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4aec728d5cf.jpg" alt="Pselected0200034.JPG" border="0" /></p>
<p>To avoid crowds who were bound for viewing the plum blossoms, and because we weren't sure about the conditions of the roads, we originally planned to get up at 4 am and set off early.</p>
<p>But then we realized that was probably too early and we wouldn't be able to see the sunlight or the blue sky. And when you're taking pictures, those are two things you can't do without!</p>
<p>So we decided to delay our departure by an hour and had breakfast. We ended up leaving Taichung at 6 am.</p>
<p>It was still dark as we set off for our destination and the streetlights illuminated the night like stars awaiting the arrival of daybreak.</p>
<p>After reaching Zhongtou from Taichung, we turned onto Provincial Highway 16. This road had amazing scenery and not much traffic; whereas Provincial Highway 14 was riddled with potholes and packed with trucks and coaches.</p>
<p>After leaving Xinyi Township, we enjoyed a pleasant drive along Provincial Highway 21 before turning onto Nantou Route 59 for a straight run through to Fengguidou and Wusonglun.</p>
<p>It was an industrial road just as expected from what we had read online. It was really narrow, ran along one side of a valley, and needed some skillful driving and navigation!</p>
<p>When we arrived it was nearly 8 o'clock. There were already a lot of cars parked at the sides of the road and the rather small parking lot at the Wusonglun campsite.</p>
<p>These industrial roads were already narrow enough without all the cars parked on both sides. This really made driving difficult when the time came for us to make our way back down the hill.</p>
<p>Anyhow, we had arrived in good time after about 2 hours of leisurely driving.</p>
<p><img title="Pselected0200047.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4af068d5aa3.jpg" alt="Pselected0200047.JPG" border="0" /></p>
<p>We could actually already see the plum trees when we turned onto the industrial road. The entire hilltop was covered with them, although it was still quite chilly at the time.</p>
<p>But when the sun came out, the plum trees took on a whole new appearance as they were illuminated by the morning light. It was almost as if they were smiling "good morning" to us :)</p>
<p><img title="Pselected0200080.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4af0d598d67.jpg" alt="Pselected0200080.JPG" border="0" /></p>
<p>Seeing the blossoms brought to life by the blue sky I just had to take some pictures...</p>
<p>The petals were still damp with early morning dew, and the whiteness of the flowers was remarkable... So pure and beautiful.</p>
<p>Even though my knees and fingers were frozen stiff in the cold morning, it was worth it just to see the blossoms.</p>
<p><img title="Pselected02selected02447.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4af17ce0da9.jpg" alt="Pselected02selected02447.JPG" border="0" /></p>
<p>The new flowers budding at the tips of the branches looked as though they could burst open with a smile at any moment under the warm glow of the sun.</p>
<p><img title="Pselected02selected02465.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4af19dc584e.jpg" alt="Pselected02selected02465.JPG" border="0" /></p>
<p>We stayed at the campsite until about 10 o'clock and then got ready to make our way back down the hill. By that time it was jam-packed with cars.</p>
<p>We had taken advantage of the lovely weather to see the blossoms and enjoy the sunshine. We were well rewarded for the effort. The early bird not only catches the worm… but also gets to see flowers! </p>
<p><img title="Pselected0200172.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4af1f2baf9d.jpg" alt="Pselected0200172.JPG" border="0" /></p>
<p>After leaving the campsite, you can follow Provincial Highway 21 north to Sun Moon Lake. In winter, the surface of Sun Moon Lake is so still and, if you're lucky, you can see snow on the tops of Hehuan Mountain.</p>
<p>If it's still early, it's not a bad idea to spend some time at Sun Moon Lake before heading home.</p>
<p>This short trip was really soothing for both body and mind. Taiwan is such a beautiful place filled with spectacular sights, sounds and smiles.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<img title="Pselected0200192.JPG" src="../../images/article/economy/selected02/4b4af2969b1cb.jpg" alt="Pselected0200192.JPG" border="0" />&nbsp;</p>
<div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Wusonglun</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address：
            
            </td>
                <td>46-1 Lumei Lane, Ziqiang Village, Xinyi Township, Nantou County</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Telephone：</td>
                <td>0921791769</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Getting there：</td>
                <td>Follow National Highway 3 to Mingjian Interchange for Mingjian, take Provincial Highway 16 to Jiji, turn onto Provincial Highway 21 at Shuili, take Provincial Highway 21 and turn onto Nantou Route 59 at 88.6 km, cross Aiguo Bridge and head for Ziai to reach the Wusonglun campsite.</td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>
        </div>
		]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>1</subjectid>
      <region>3</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/300?category=economy</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/family/selected05/</folder>
      <title>A Family Trip to the Coast of Hualien</title>
      <subtitle>Renowned for its mountains, coastline and breathtaking scenery, Hualien has always been one of our favorite spots. Aside from the stunning views and delicious food that you encounter as you explore areas, the magnificent landscape that cleanses and calms both the body and the soul is what really attracts its visitors.</subtitle>
      <author>By 紫色微笑</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[<p>Our family visits the beautiful Hualien and Taitung almost every year. They have so much to offer with their amazing scenery along the road and delicious food. Even though I've already been there so many times, I don't feel as if I've experienced it all. The magnificent landscape that cleanses and calms both the body and the soul is what really attracts its visitors.</p>
<p>As we really wanted to eat Yuli noodles last time we came, we were willing to drive there as our stomachs rumbled with hunger all the way (there were a lot of convenience stores and it would have been simple to just get out of the car and buy some food). Anyway, you must pass through Yuli if you take the Hualien-Taitung East Rift Valley Highway, so you can't miss it.</p>
  <img src="../../images/article/family/selected05/family_bigpic.jpg" width="627" height="276" class="selected_pic" />

<p>The facade and seating area of the restaurant looked pretty much the same as other similar small establishments.</p>
<p>This is a bowl of soup noodles. I don't know if you noticed, but it's an amazing bowl of soup noodles. It's so good that people have been raving about it on the internet. Hey, its reputation is well deserved: the quantity was hug even though I ordered a small one, and I couldn't believe how many noodles there were. I forgot to use an object in the photo for a size comparison. Even though I had a small bowl, it was much bigger than what I would usually consider to be a large bowl.</p>
<p>Even their dry noodles were pretty good; kind of like thinner eggnoodles. They were even softer and more chewy than other eggnoodles. As for the taste... Hehe... The noodles weren't very special but they definitely were very well worth it.</p>
<img src="../../images/article/family/selected05/family_pic1.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/family/selected05/family_pic2.jpg" /><p>We headed north along Guangfeng Road, which connects the Hualien-Taitung Highway and coast road, admiring Hualien's beautiful coastal scenery as we made our way to the Adagio Inn where we would be staying for the night. We'd already arranged to stay at the Adagio Inn and just wanted to enjoy the inn itself, so we didn't really plan any sightseeing along the way; we just hurried to make it there for the check-in time. Haha, it's quite ironic that we hurried to a place called 'Adagio'!</p>
<p>The inn was an amazing place to stay. From the moment we stepped into our room, we could feel their unique approach to hospitality. We had stayed at lots of nice places, but I was so impressed by the hospitality of the staff at Adagio. The design of the room was minimalist and nothing extravagant, but I could see the thoughtful design that went into everything. The room was also really big, so our baby could crawl around happily. For us, being able to enjoy a place like that, slowing down and lazing the day away is the best way to relieve stress.</p>
<p>The inn doesn't have many rooms, so all of their guests not only have a great space to spend time, but also can enjoy the sea view. The following morning, we woke up especially early to see the first ray of the day. We watched the sun gradually rise over the surface of the ocean and the golden sunshine pierce the darkness of the night before dawn. Waking up in time to see the dawn wasn't easy, but it was definitely worth it.</p>
<p>At night, we strolled under a night sky free of light pollution. The three of us counted the stars in the dark. It was so romantic. It's impossible to do that in the city!</p>
<img src="../../images/article/family/selected05/family_pic3.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/family/selected05/family_pic4.jpg" /><p>After we checked out, we went to Shitiping near the inn. Because of the geography of this area, some of the strange rocks by the sea have a white color. As they reflected the intense sunlight, it felt as if you're in a snowfield. It's so dazzling that you couldn't open your eyes. Of course we took a walk down to the beach. There you can walk on the tidal flats and see  the seaweed  and creatures. The unique scenery of that coast will stay with us for a long time.</p>
<p>Shitiping Harbor was the first place in Hualien for whale watching. So other than Hualien Harbor, you can also go there for a whale watching trip! Try it and you'll have a whale of a time!</p>
<p>The coastal scenery of Hualien and Taitung doesn't only attract local visitors; it's a must-see even for tourists from China. The three of us had such a great time on this trip and it also brought us closer together. We'll definitely be back again when we get time!</p>

    </div>
    
        <div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Yuli Noodles</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address：
            
            </td>
                <td>No. 76, Section 2, Zhongshan Rd, Yuli Township, Hualien County</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Telephone：</td>
                <td>03-888-1613 / AM7:00~PM7:00 (open 365 days a year)</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Transportation：</td>
                <td>
                Take Provincial Highway 9, turn onto Guangfu Rd, Yuli Township, then turn onto Section 2, Zhongshan Rd, Yuli Township and you will soon arrive at Yuli Noodles at no. 76.<br />
  Take the train to Yuli Station, walk along Guangfu Rd, then turn right onto Section 2, Zhongshan Rd and you will soon arrive at Yuli Noodles at no. 76.
  
                  </td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>2</subjectid>
      <region>2</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/0?category=family</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/family/selected01/</folder>
      <title>A Trip to Shirding Nature Park to see "Bambi"</title>
      <subtitle>
        You can book an expert guide to help you understand the rich, natural ecology of Shirding Nature Park as well as have a close encounter with some sika deer.
      </subtitle>
      <author>帆帆貓</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[
          <p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461979.jpg"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4559" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840954-1070178946.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4559" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>The main reason for this trip to Kenting was to visit Shirding Nature Park and see the cute sika deer.</span></p>
<p>This species of deer is in the same deer family as the beloved cartoon character “Bambi”.  When we visited Green Island, we only managed to see deer tracks during the night.</p>
<p>Only around 1,000 of these animals remain on Green Island and venison is still sold there.</p>
<p>Therefore the numbers available for repopulation are limited. (It is necessary to emphasize that the killing will end when the demand ends!)</p>
<p>Thanks to the hard work of the local residents, Shirding Nature Park has successfully increased the population of sika deer to over 3,000 that is inspiring news.</p>
<p>Although the park is not just about the sika deer, there are also many birds to be seen singing in the treetops.</p>
<p>The bird in the first picture is a Gray Tree Pie.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39512329"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4613" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344866978-1160706190.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4613" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The Shirding community is located near the Kenting Forest Recreation Area and is the brainchild of the local residents.</p>
<p>They have people on patrol every evening to protect the ecology of Shirding Nature Park.</p>
<p>They also conduct park ecology tours. If you want to know what plants and animals there are in Shirding Nature Park,</p>
<p>you can book an ecology tour with the community so that you can gain a deeper understanding of Shirding Nature Park.</p>
<p>Conical bamboo hats and walking sticks can also be borrowed on site to make it easier for people to hike up the hills. The local residents really are a kind bunch.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461967"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4606" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840949-54170774.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4606" border="0"></span></a><span> &nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The guide responsible for our tour was Secretary-General Zhao.</p>
<p>He told us that the Shirding area was once called “Guizijiao” and is located in the middle of Kenting National Park.</p>
<p>It was formerly a settlement of the Paiwan aboriginal tribe and was an early site of the sinicization of indigenous people in Taiwan.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461969"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4619" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840950-1663375741.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4619" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>This is a kiln structure that was once used to fire charcoal. Secretary-General Zhao told us that such lime kilns were always used to boil water and cook food. They are extremely tough and durable.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39512333"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4636" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344866979-1940841184.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4636" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>A passageway formed from coral rocks and the trees above.</p>
<p>Constant attacks by northeasterly monsoon winds created extraordinary windswept trees.</p>
<p>In the daytime, you can appreciate the unique patterns on the coral rocks.</p>
<p>In the evening, you can see lots of insects having a get-together.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39512331"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4635" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344866978-3698409855.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4635" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>You can see macaques swinging through this forest if you are lucky.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39512339"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4570" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344866980-500502439.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4570" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>we finally arrived at the main attraction, the sika deer conservation area, by noon after walking for an hour.</p>
<p>The scenery is exquisite; there is a vast prairie and a natural lake which is like a paradise for sika deer.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461975"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4737" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840952-4006205335.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4737" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>It is not easy to catch a glimpse of the sika deer straight away. They are naturally timid</p>
<p>and spend most of the daytime hiding in the undergrowth.</p>
<p>We had no choice but to make a little noise to make them come running out.</p>
<p>We could see the deer very clearly even though there was a great distance between us and the herd.</p>
<p>I just could not stop thinking about how cute they were.</p>
<p>I heard that they sometimes stray to roads at night.</p>
<p>That is why the speed limit on the mountain roads around here is 15 km/h. Remember to drive carefully.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462009"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4736" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840964-3741744782.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4736" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>I do not know if you have ever seen the instant noodle commercial in which a woman said  that the man was thoughtless.</p>
<p>The man ended up shouting from his car using a megaphone.</p>
<p>I heard that commercial was shot on the road in front of this sea view.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461977"><span><img title="D3100_DSC_4746" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840953-2155150626.jpg" alt="D3100_DSC_4746" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>If your neck is aching from looking up, you can take a look downward. If you have good eyesight, you will be able to see crickets on the green leaves.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461989"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4581" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840957-3477699767.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4581" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>As the Papilio helenus fortunius Fruhstorfer drank nectar, it was concentrating so deeply that it did not even notice that anyone was there.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461993"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4642" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840958-4271901686.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4642" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The bananas that grow in the park are the main food for the macaques. This bunch was not ripe yet so was best to be avoided.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39461995"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4682" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840959-1610952935.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4682" border="0"></span></a><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>Seeing these reminded me of Aiyaya, the Ganoderma lucidum elf from the TV show 'Sacred Arrow of Spirit Mountain'.</p>
<p>I am not sure whether or not that gives away my age. :$</p>
<p>Ganoderma lucidum are quite expensive; it is expressly written that it is forbidden to pick them.</p>
<p>Even so, there are still people who only think of short-term profit and pick them to sell.</p>
<p>I am a firm believer that photographs should be the only things you take away with you.</p>
<p>That is the only way to preserve this beautiful scenery for future generations.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462001"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4686" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840961-3934370562.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4686" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The Megacrania tsudai Shiraki insect is a class II protected insect.</p>
<p>They can only be found in Kenting and on Green Island.</p>
<p>It is a species unique to Taiwan and hides among Screw Pine leaves. The edges of Screw Pine leaves are like the blade of a saw.</p>
<p>They have extremely hard saw-like teeth, meaning that Megacrania tsudai Shiraki are not easy for predators to catch.</p>
<p>These stick insects are also able to emit a distinctive odor if they encounter danger.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462015"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_4778" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840967-860195062.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_4778" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>Shirding Nature Park also has a lot to offer if you come in search of sika deer at night.</p>
<p>The first thing we came across was a very well-fed looking Gray Tree Pie.</p>
<p>It had a plump body and fluffy feathers. We probably woke it up; it was a little slow to respond.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462025"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5147" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840971-500444708.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5147" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>When we saw lots of pairs of eyes shining in the night, it was then we realized that a heard of deer had appeared.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462017"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5101" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840968-794571307.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5101" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>The most surprising thing was that there were poisonous snakes like this Deinagkistrodon acutus pit viper in the undergrowth.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462019"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5136" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840969-2025211048.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5136" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>It was silently lying in wait for its prey but slithered into the undergrowth when it saw people coming.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462021"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5142" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840970-2655952490.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5142" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>When night falls, the coral rock that we saw during the day is where creepy-crawlies meet for a get-together. This Tetragnatha nepiformis spider was waiting for its prey to arrive. <a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462029"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5156" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840971-1422945576.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5156" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>There was also a Camaena batanica pancala snail stuck to the face of the rock.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462031"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5158" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840972-3634844621.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5158" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>This is another of Taiwan's venomous creatures: the Black widow spider! You do not want to get bitten by one of these.</p>
<p>I checked Wikipedia and it said that they only have a small quantity of venom.</p>
<p>It also said that the venom is seldom fatal to humans.</p>
<p>If you have got a friend who is especially brave, you can do an experiment using their finger. XD</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462033"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5164" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840973-2949679708.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5164" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>There are also Trimeresurus mucrosquamatus pit vipers in the park, but they stay hidden in the undergrowth unless you deliberately try to approach them.</p>
<p>It is not usually a problem to observe them from a distance.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462035"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5179" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840974-1677994120.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5179" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>Even the crabs look particularly alert at night.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462037"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5185" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840975-659281739.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5185" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>A toad. From the expression on its face, it looked as if it was pondering the big questions of life.</p>
<p><a href="http://fanfancat.pixnet.net/album/photo/39462039"><span><img title="D7000_DSC_5199" src="../../images/article/family/selected01/1344840976-3879153137.jpg" alt="D7000_DSC_5199" border="0"></span></a></p>
<p>Other than sika deer, Kenting has so many plants and animals to see.</p>
<p>Next time you come, why not book a tour? I guarantee it will be worth your while!</p>
<p>Association for Shirding Community Development <a href="http://www.shirding.org.tw/index.htm" target="_blank"><span>http://www.shirding.org.tw/index.htm</span></a><br><span>Telephone：08-8862720&nbsp;&nbsp;<span class="style13">(service hours 08:00~17:00)</span><br>Fax：08-8856978<br>E-mail：</span><a href="mailto:shirding1@yahoo.com.tw"><span>shirding1@yahoo.com.tw</span></a></p>
<p>Getting there：<br />★ By car: <br />Provincial Highway 17 (West Coast Highway): Drive until you reach Pingtung County and turn onto Provincial Highway 1 after passing through Shuidiliao, pass Fenggang and join Provincial Highway 26, drive through Hengchun to Kenting, enter the Kenting Forest Recreation Area archway, turn right at the fork in the road to reach Shirding Nature Park. <br /> Provincial Highway:Pass Fenggang and join Provincial Highway 26, drive through Hengchun to Kenting, enter the Kenting Forest Recreation Area archway, turn right at the fork in the road to reach Shirding Nature Park. <br /> ◎From Taitung: Take Provincial Highway 9, pass Daren Township, pass Fenggang and join Provincial Highway 26, drive through Hengchun to Kenting, enter the Kenting Forest Recreation Area archway, turn right at the fork in the road to reach Shirding Nature Park.</p>
<div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Shirding Nature Park</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address：
            
            </td>
                <td>Hengchun, Pingtung County</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Telephone：</td>
                <td>08-8862720 <br />
                (service hours 8:00~17:00)</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Getting there：</td>
                <td>★ By car: <br />National Highway：Drive in the direction of Kenting from the end of the freeway, join Provincial Highway 17 (West Coast Highway), turn onto Provincial Highway 1 after passing through Shuidiliao, pass Fenggang and join Provincial Highway 26, drive through Hengchun to Kenting, enter the Kenting Forest Recreation Area archway, turn right at the fork in the road to reach Shirding Nature Park. </td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>
        </div>
          ]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>2</subjectid>
      <region>4</region>
	  <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/90?category=family</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/luxury/selected05/</folder>
      <title>The Blue Skies, Ocean, Sandy Beaches, Water Activities, Spa and Great Hotels in Southern Taiwan</title>
      <subtitle>If you asked me "Where in Taiwan is the most typical southern vacation spot with blue skies, white clouds, sandy beaches and bikinis?" I'd have to say "Kenting".</subtitle>
      <author>By 大方</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[<p>Now that we have the high-speed rail, it's more convenient to visit Kenting from Taipei. When it comes to vacation hotels in Kenting, my favorite has to be Caesar Park Hotel. Not only does it have a five-star rating, but it also has an awesome sandy beach. It's amazing to go down to the beach to swim, sunbathe, listen to music, or paddle a canoe.</p>  
  <img src="../../images/article/luxury/selected05/luxury_bigpic2.jpg" width="627" height="276" class="selected_pic" />
<p>There are various ways to get to Kenting Caesar Park Hotel. If you are from Taipei, I suggest you to take the Uni Airline direct flights, departing on Tuesday, Thursday and Saturday for Hengchun Airport. This is the fastest way. But the high-speed rail is also very convenient. Just call the hotel to reserve a shuttle bus the day before you arrive. There's one shuttle bus per day and you can take it from just outside the station.
</p>
<p>I hadn't been to Caesar Park Hotel for almost 2 years. This time I felt impressed . The staff at the entrance was really friendly; it's reaching the standard that you'd expect from a famous five-star hotel abroad. They led me to the check-in desk, and my luggage was taken to my room afterwards. The quality of service had obviously increased. Well done!
</p>
<p>Why do I like Caesar Park Hotel? I think it's because of their unbeatable huge swimming pool that provides whole day of fun for my entire family. The pool is divided into parent-and-child area, standard area and deep area. Under the supervision of the lifegaurds, you don't need to worry about the safety for your young children.</p>
<p>Maybe some people don't really care about the pool, but the ocean and the white sandy beach right at the doorstep of Caesar Park are breathtaking. Besides trying out some water activities, you can also hire an instructor to take you out for canoeing. If you're tired, you can just relax on a sunlounger with parasol, enjoying a cold beverage and the beautiful ocean. Your worries will all drift away. 
</p>
<p>This beach is great for canoeing. Put on your lifejacket and an instructor will tell you what to do. I had a tall, handsome instructor to teach me how to paddle. It's tricky but not too difficult; you just need to get the hang of it and you'll be moving forward.
</p>
<img src="../../images/article/luxury/selected05/luxury_bigpic.jpg" width="627" height="276" /><br />
<p>I don't think anyone would believe this picture was taken in Taiwan. You can see greenery all around Caesar Park. Even if you sit at the balcony of the 2nd floor, you'll still feel yourself on vacation.
</p>
<p>I've always thought that Caesar Park's rooms are excellent. They offer comfortable spaces for you to relax. The transparent bathroom makes the room feel more spacious. It also feels great to bathe in the large free-standing bathtub.
</p>

  <img src="../../images/article/luxury/selected05/luxury_pic3.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/luxury/selected05/luxury_pic4.jpg" />
<p>Caesar Park offers various types of rooms, each type with something unique. This time I reserved a room on the 1st floor; it was designed like a private villa with a private balcony. I sat in the jacuzzi on the balcony and listened to the sounds of the birds and the insects. You could look up to see the moon and stars. It was heavenly.
</p>
<p>There was another small space next to the balcony to be used as a private space for relaxing and reading without being disturbed. You rarely see design like this on a balcony. This is just one appeal of Caesar Park's rooms. Moreover, you just have to look up to enjoy the spectacle of Dajianshan Mountain in Kenting National Park.
</p>
<p>The room I stayed in adopted the Japanese style, using plenty of wood. The room felt so warm and comfortable. I loved it.
</p>
<p>Good food is something a hotel can't do without. Caesar Park provides both Chinese and Western cuisine and a bar. It also provides seasonal specialties such as onion, flying fish and tuna. I still remember there was a summer barbecue outside last time I was at Caesar Park. It was awesome.
</p>
<p>During this stay, I enjoyed a spring suite cooked with local ingredients. The suite included cherry blossom shrimp rolls and flying fish roe sausages; chicken soup with lady bell, angular Solomon's seal, lotus seeds and Job's Tears; and scrambled eggs with Hengchun onion and roe. It was a good chance to taste some great southern Taiwanese food.
</p>
<p>Nighttime is when Kenting Street really comes to life. The main street is only a 5 minute walk from Caesar Park. The crowded Kenting Street has snacks, restaurants, accessories, clothes... everything you can imagine. There's good atmosphere, good food and good shopping. You won't have to worry about getting bored at night. Come and enjoy the Kenting Street! Kenting Street changes every year. It's packed with restaurants and, of course, snacks that can never be overlooked.</p>
<p>If you want to buy swimwear or clothes, you can find them on the main street. There are also lots of souvenirs, so make sure you have enough money with you, haha. Huang's Mung Beans with Garlic in Checheng deserves a mention. It's an old restaurant that's highly regarded by the locals. There you can eat mung beans on ice, something that's not easy to find in Taipei. It's cheap and the servings are big.
</p>
<p>So what are you waiting for? Give Kenting a try. Put a smile on your face, head to Kenting and indulge in some great food. What more could you expect?</p>

    </div>
    
        <div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Caesar Park Hotel - Kenting + Kenting Street + Kenting Food</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address：
            
            </td>
                <td>Hengchun Township, Kenting County</td>
              </tr>
              
              <tr>
                <td>Transportation：</td>
                <td>Drive to Kenting, or take the high-speed train to Zuoying Station and take a shuttle bus.</td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>3</subjectid>
      <region>4</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/0?category=luxury</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/luxury/selected03/</folder>
      <title>The Pride of Hokkaido: Adorably Delicate, Yet Delicious Cheesecakes by Kou Cheese</title>
      <subtitle>
        The sumptuous aroma and texture of Kou Cheese brought back memories of the first time we tasted gourmet cheesecake in Hokkaido. It was an amazing time.
      </subtitle>
      <author>Nata</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[
          <p><span><img title="01" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771304-1419575692.jpg" alt="01" border="0"><br>
		  After stepping out into the fresh air and glimmering sunlight of the shopping streets around the CMP Block Museum of Arts, we noticed a bright yellow flag that read '<span style="color: #ff6600;">Freshly baked!</span>' grabbing the attention of passers-by. Before long, we found our noses tantalized by the aroma of freshly baked cakes. I could not stop thinking how amazing the smell was. Naturally, my mouth started watering.<br><br><br>
		  <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772534"><span><img title="02" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771305-1732595662.jpg" alt="02" border="0"></span></a><br><span><span style="color: #ff6600;">Kou Cheese</span> opened in July this year and sells a selection of delectable cheesecakes.  It is located near the charming CMP Block Museum of Arts and is a major temptation for anyone who is a fan of high-quality cakes. <br />
<span style="background-color: #d8c2e7;">(I am just one of the many people they enticed. I bought a box of their Half-Baked No. 2 cakes in August and luckily got another opportunity to visit again at the beginning of September. I was ecstatic!)</span><br><br><br>
</span><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772542"><span><img title="05" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771306-2851915728.jpg" alt="05" border="0"></span></a><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772598"><span><img title="26" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771314-1498691287.jpg" alt="26" border="0"></span></a><br>
<span>The eye-catching 'Freshly baked!' flag lets customers know that their delicious cheesecakes have just come out of the oven. It is such an original idea; I love it!<br><br><br>
</span><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772536"><span><img title="03" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771305-177890782.jpg" alt="03" border="0"></span></a><br>
<span>The name 'Kou' originally means 'relaxing and pleasant' in Japanese but also has the deeper meanings of 'brightness', 'joy' and 'enthusiasm for life'. Indeed, these cheesecakes were the brainchild of a group of idealistic young people!<br><br><br>
</span><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772538"><span><img title="04" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771305-1135041013.jpg" alt="04" border="0"></span></a><br>
<span>The facade consisting of white frames and large panes of glass creates an air of refinement and professionalism.</span><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/blog/post/27091853" target="_blank"><strong><span>CHOCO MISSION, before Kou Cheese opened.</span></strong></a><span><br><br><br>
</span><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772544"><span><img title="07" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771306-4066580762.jpg" alt="07" border="0"></span></a><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772554"><span><img title="08" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771307-3310170204.jpg" alt="08" border="0"></span></a><br>After walking through the front door, the first thing you notice is the minimalistic design fusing classical Western objects and art. This is interspersed with an American retro style, creating an atmosphere that is both elegant and slightly playful.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772556"><img title="09" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771307-3582314808.jpg" alt="09" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772552"><img title="10" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771308-3586789739.jpg" alt="10" border="0"></a>&nbsp;<br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772558"><img title="11" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771308-561789480.jpg" alt="11" border="0"></a><br>The wooden tables in the middle of the shop display raw ingredients, packaging, and jams. This gives the place an appealing rustic image.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772564"><img title="14" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771309-2564157372.jpg" alt="14" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772570"><img title="15" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771309-1449557357.jpg" alt="15" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772568"><img title="16" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771310-3257741891.jpg" alt="16" border="0"></a><br>The freshly made jams have flavors like banana and strawberry, lemon and guava, and passion fruit and mango. You can ask for the price if you are interested.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772578"><img title="19" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771311-2977044160.jpg" alt="19" border="0"></a>&nbsp;&nbsp;<br><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772576"><img title="18" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771311-1844473613.jpg" alt="18" border="0"></a><br>The unique, laid-back interior design makes everyone who visits feel relaxed and at ease.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772580"><img title="20" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771312-3309238557.jpg" alt="20" border="0"></a><br>CMP Block Museum of Arts: <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/blog/post/31050211" target="_blank"><strong>Visiting the Drop-in Hut and Portuguese Umbrella Street!</strong></a><br><br>
</span><span>Lots of people who are tired from walking around the CMP Block Museum of Arts come to Kou Cheese to relax with a box of delicious cheesecakes or to quench their thirst with a fruit juice soda or ice-cream. You really cannot beat a nice rest with a lovely piece of cake.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772562"><img title="13" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771309-3663710293.jpg" alt="13" border="0"></a><br>Are you wondering why I called this cheesecake the "<span style="color: #3366ff;">pride of Hokkaido</span>"?<br>
It is because the main ingredient is 100% fresh milk produced in southern Hokkaido. This milk is made into cream cheese in the city of Hakodate within 120 minutes of the cows being milked. It contains only 1/3 of the emulsifiers and salt of regular cream cheese in order to better bring out the pure flavor of Hokkaido milk.<br><br><br><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772560"><img title="12" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771308-1241237602.jpg" alt="12" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772610"><img title="32" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771316-3786588531.jpg" alt="32" border="0"></a><br>
All of the raw ingredients come from Japan. As well as the cream cheese from Hokkaido, there are also high-quality ingredients including special-grade Nisshin Violet Flour and coarse Wasanbon sugar. A half-steamed, half-baked method is used to create the adorably delicate half-baked cheesecakes.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772572"><img title="17" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771310-1278384058.jpg" alt="17" border="0"></a><br>The counter<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772584"><img title="21" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771312-2362542966.jpg" alt="21" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772588"><img title="22" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771312-2224533555.jpg" alt="22" border="0"></a><br><span style="color: #fd67d3;"><strong>Ice-cream</strong></span>(flavors are seasonal): One flavor <span style="color: #ff0000;">78 NTD</span>, two flavors <span style="color: #ff0000;">128 NTD </span><br>
The ice-cream flavors available on the day we visited were cheese, kumquat, watermelon, and passion fruit.<br>Just like the cheesecakes, the cheese flavor ice-cream is also made using cheese from southern Hokkaido. When I first put it in my mouth, I thought that it tasted refreshing with does not have much flavor but after it melted on my tongue, it gave off a subtle cheesy aroma. The taste is truly unique. It is their most popular flavor of ice-cream. The other ice-cream flavors made using local Taiwanese fruits change according to the seasons. I loved the natural tanginess and mild sweetness of the kumquat flavor; with the added taste of cranberry jelly, it was the perfect combination.<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772596"><img title="25" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771313-224434517.jpg" alt="25" border="0"></a><br>The cute girl working at the counter made a fruit soda with ice-cream for us to try. You can choose any flavor soda and add a big scoop of ice-cream to create your ideal drink!<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772590"><img title="23" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771313-4090243109.jpg" alt="23" border="0"></a><br>
<span style="color: #fd67d3;"><strong>Cranberry juice soda + cheese ice-cream:</strong></span>／<span style="color: #ff0000;">138 NTD<br></span>This was Damao's drink. It was so pink and appetizing; it looked like it had been very lovingly prepared!<br><br><br><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772592"><img title="24" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771313-970528272.jpg" alt="24" border="0"></a><br>
I chose <span style="color: #fd67d3;"><strong>kumquat juice soda + passion fruit ice-cream.</strong></span> The gentle effervescence of the drink really raises your spirits just like the fizzy bubbles. I used the pastel colored spoon to scoop out the tasty passion fruit ice-cream and used the straw to drink the refreshing fruit juice soda. The combination of sweet and sour taste is really invigorating and  the perfect way to unwind!<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772602"><img title="27" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771314-4158034602.jpg" alt="27" border="0"></a><br>Next up was the main event: Time to evaluate the half-baked cheesecakes. A friendly assistant brought to us a tray of stunning golden-yellow cheesecakes. We had to take out our cameras and snap some pictures. The assistant was just as pretty and dainty as the cakes; it was a perfect scene!<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772600"><img title="28" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771315-2861285816.jpg" alt="28" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772604"><img title="29" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771315-3262700596.jpg" alt="29" border="0"></a><br><span style="color: #fd67d3;"><strong>Half-Baked No.1:</strong></span>Box of 4<span style="color: #ff0000;">150 NTD </span>; Box of 6<span style="color: #ff0000;">225 NTD </span><span style="color: #999999;">(average price 37.5 NTD each)</span><br>
The Half-Baked No. 1 cheesecakes have a light cheese texture. They are incredibly smooth and the subtle aroma of cheese is sheer delight.<br>It is not often that I eat light cheesecakes and consider them to be really delicious. However, these might just be the best I have ever tasted!<br><br><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772606"><img title="30" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771315-1050701354.jpg" alt="30" border="0"></a> <a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772608"><img title="31" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771316-803950238.jpg" alt="31" border="0"></a><br><span style="color: #fd67d3;"><strong>Half-Baked No. 2:</strong></span>Box of 4 <span style="color: #ff0000;">200 NTD </span>; Box of 6 <span style="color: #ff0000;">300 NTD </span><span style="color: #999999;">(average price 50 NTD each)<br></span>These are sumptuous, heavier-textured cheesecakes that are rich but not overpowering in taste. The thin layer of sponge cake adds delicacy and natural sweetness.<br>With their milky aroma, the Half-Baked No. 2 cheesecakes have a much stronger cheesy taste than the Half-Baked No. 1 variety. The slight honey-like sweetness actually comes from the process of steaming and baking the Wasanbon sugar; you may be mistaken for thinking they were made using honey!<br><br><br><a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772546"><img title="06" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771306-1043957054.jpg" alt="06" border="0"></a><br>
<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772612"><img title="33" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771316-1204681338.jpg" alt="33" border="0"></a><br>The card boxes have been designed to serve as picnic boxes. The card fork at the top is a nice little touch. With our box of cheesecakes in hand, we went for a walk through the CMP Block Museum of Arts!<br><img title="icon_notice01-i02.gif" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/4afe655896269.gif" alt="icon_notice01-i02.gif" border="0">&nbsp;The two varieties of half-baked cheesecake described above are only sold by the box; you cannot buy them individually.<br><br>Even though the No. 1 and No. 2 cheesecakes are small and will be gone in only two or three bites, you cannot really bemoan the price. The exquisite texture and flavor of the high-quality cheese cakes are worth every dollar. <br />
<span style="background-color: #ffff99;">(In future, the shop will sell their unique 6-inch Spiral Spirit cake. If you like your cheesecakes large, you can join their Facebook fan page and keep an eye out for details.)</span><br><br><br>&nbsp;<a href="http://nw0912.pixnet.net/album/photo/181772616"><img title="34" src="../../images/article/luxury/selected03/1346771316-3781832774.jpg" alt="34" border="0"></a><br>
The sumptuous aroma and texture of Kou Cheese brought back memories of the first time we tasted gourmet cheesecake in Hokkaido. It was an amazing time, with the natural rich flavor of pure milk, the gorgeous weather, the fresh air, and the soft light of Hokkaido.<br></span></p>
<div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Kou Cheese</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address: 
            
            </td>
                <td>No. 257-3, Section 1, Taizhonggang Road, Taichung</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Telephone: </td>
                <td>04-23295797</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Getting there: </td>
                <td>No. 257-3, Section 1, Taizhonggang Road, Taichung (near the CMP Block Museum of Arts)</td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>
        </div>
          ]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>3</subjectid>
      <region>3</region>
	  <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/177?category=luxury</link>
    </article>
    <article>
      <folder>/images/article/myself/selected05/</folder>
      <title>Qishan, a Photographer's Dreamland: The Beauty and Colors of a Fairy Tale</title>
      <subtitle>Qishan is where Kaohsiung's mountainous area begins. It's a lively little town with a railroad station from a fairy tale, streets adorned with stone archways, a cathedral and golden bananas. Qishan is still awash with history!</subtitle>
      <author>By 640</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[<p>Traveling alone is great. You can do anything as you please without compromising with anyone else. You only have to think of yourself: go and stop wherever you want, and go home whenever you want.</p>

  <img src="../../images/article/myself/selected05/self_bigpic.jpg" width="627" height="276" class="selected_pic" /><div class="selected_mark">
</div><p>I may be all alone, but I know how to enjoy my own company. Every time I set off with my backpack, it takes courage to face the ups and downs of the open road!</p>
<br />
<p>This time, I grabbed my camera, stepped into the warm sunlight of southern Taiwan and headed to Qishan. Qishan is where Kaohsiung's mountainous area begins. It's a lively little town with a railroad station from a fairy tale, streets adorned with stone archways, a cathedral and golden bananas. Qishan is still awash with history! If you're after characterful old streets, good food and fun, Qishan is for you!</p>
<p>Qishan Station gracefully combines Western and Japanese architectural elements. It's simple and elegant, and it gives you a nice, warm feeling. It's as beautiful as a cute gingerbread house from a fairy tale.
</p>
<img src="../../images/article/myself/selected05/self_pic1.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/myself/selected05/self_pic2.jpg" /><p>This cute wooden railroad station is unique in Taiwan. To me, it's Qishan's most distinctive landmark. The history of Qishan Station is full of trouble and misfortune; it's been consumed by fire many times, and there was even a plan to demolish it. It was only after years of protest by many artists and literary figures that it was preserved, renovated and brought back into use.</p>
<p>The stone corridors are reminiscent of Renaissance architecture. Their distinctive construction and solemn arches are both imposing and harmonious.</p>
<p>Baroque-style houses line the streets. Their elegance and grandeur tell us about the prosperity of times gone by.</p>
<p>Qishan Primary School is over 100 years old. A sight that's definitely worth seeing is the school's assembly hall with its Roman-style gables.</p>
<p>The auditorium, northern classroom building and teachers' office at the Cishan Living Cultural Park (formerly Gushan Elementary School) are historical buildings that are bathed in a carefree atmosphere and an aura of culture.</p>

<p>The beautifully colorful wall tells an extraordinary story.</p>
<img src="../../images/article/myself/selected05/self_pic3.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/myself/selected05/self_pic4.jpg" /><p>The white walls emanate a distinctly French je ne sais quoi, and it's amazing to bask in the afternoon sun here.</p>
<p>As part of the Let's Color Taiwan project, the walls of the Qishan Early Intervention Center were painted to give children with special needs at the center the opportunity to experience painting. The inspiration and stimulation they acquire from the usage of colors are beneficial for their learning and development, and thus their living environment is also improved.</p>
<p>The colorful art in the community also creates a different visual sensation, which attracts more visitors and contributes to the ambiance of the Qishan area.</p>
<p>Last but not least, I visited the largest Confucius Temple in Asia. I have to warn you, you'll have to climb numerous steps to get there! Qishan's Confucian temple is majestic. You feel like you're waking around inside a palace. You would be forgiven for thinking you'd stepped back in time to an imperial court in ancient China.</p>
<p>This trip to Qishan, just me and my camera, gave me a chance to marvel at the historical buildings and take lots of photos of various architectural styles. It was all so carefree and enjoyable.</p>
<p>I think everyone needs to have their own secret place, where he or she can escape to and clear their head when life becomes too complicated. Even though Qishan will always be Qishan, each year I discover different aspects of it, and a new warmth that arouses new moods and feelings.</p>
<p>Even if you're all alone, you are your own best company. Just learn to love traveling alone,  and off you go! Set off and enjoy the time by yourself.</p>

    </div>
    
        <div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Old Streets of the "Banana Town" Qishan</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address：
            
            </td>
                <td>Fuxing St, Zhongshan Rd and Huazhong St area, Qishan District, Kaohsiung</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Transportation：</td>
                <td>By scooter - Start at Kaohsiung Station, take Provincial Highway 1, at Fengpíng 2nd Rd turn left onto Jiuhe Rd, follow Provincial Highway 21 until you reach downtown Qishan.</td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>4</subjectid>
      <region>4</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/0?category=myself</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/myself/selected03/</folder>
      <title>Take a Walk Through the Lanes of Taipei to Qingtian Geo 76</title>
      <subtitle>
        It’s a good excuse to get away by yourself for a stroll through an urban oasis. This is the most beautiful street in Taipei, where the unmissable old house is situated.
      </subtitle>
      <author>Brenda Chien</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[
          <p><img title="青田街" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349877598-2237861359_n.jpg" alt="青田街" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Qingtian Street is located along the perimeter of the Shida shopping area in Taipei. The street is rich in history and culture, while lined with lush greenery. The Shida shopping area always bustles with crowds of people, food stalls and small shops.</p>
<p>However, if you walk to the end of Shida Road and turning into Qingtian Street, you will find yourself in a place that is tranquil, secluded and relaxing, yet exciting at the same time. The atmosphere is completely different.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Qingtian Street Impressions</strong></p>
<p>I first got to know about this street because my friend lives there.</p>
<p>When other old friends from Taipei heard that this friend's husband has a house on Qingtian Street, they all think she must be quite well off!</p>
<p>I later heard that Qingtian Street has the title "The Emerald of Taipei". As the name suggests, the most famous thing about Qingtian Street is that it has preserved its lush greenery. As you walk along the street, both sides are lined with large trees. Sometimes you will see trees one after another; sometimes you will see a huge old tree standing between two apartment buildings.</p>
<p>The tranquil greenery combined with the old apartment buildings, modern low-rise buildings and old Japanese-style houses that line the street serve amplify the elegance of the area.</p>
<p>It's a great place to visit in the morning or afternoon, alone or with a few friends.</p>
<p>I believe that with the warm sunshine, leafy tranquility and beautiful old buildings, all surrounded by an ambiance of refinement, one cannot help but fall in love with this unique street.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Heritage & Geosciences</strong></p>
<p>Many houses that once belonged to famous people are situated along Qingtian Street. It is also the location of the most well preserved Japanese-style houses in Taiwan.</p>
<p>Among these, the most famous one with the greatest cultural pedigree is Qingtian Geo 76!</p>
<p>I could not believe that I have lived in Taipei for over 10 years and this was my first visit ever. I was deeply moved by this beautiful little corner of the city.</p>
<p><img title="青田七六" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-1147626230_n.jpg" alt="青田七六" border="0" /></p>
<p>This Japanese-style house was built almost 80 years ago and was home to Tingying Ma, a professor of geology at National Taiwan University. To commemorate the contributions Professor Ma made to the construction development in Taiwan, Qingtian Geo 76 is not just a café but also provides in-depth tours that present topics on the story of the house, the geology of Taiwan and the architecture of the building. The English'Heritage & Geosciences' clearly illustrates the significance of the house.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4048" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-2575430365_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4048" border="0" /></p>
<p>The entrance to Qingtian Geo 76. I never expected that I could be surrounded by tall buildings one minute, then step into Qingtian Street and enjoy the leafy shade. I would come across this old house that is like a gateway to a completely different world.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4041" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-3270677870_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4041" border="0" /></p>
<p>As soon as you walk through the entrance, you are greeted by an old pine tree towering over you. The clever combination of plants with the huge taro leaves growing in front of the tree puts you at ease and almost makes you feel as if you are in the mountains.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4042" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-2097026500_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4042" border="0" /></p>
<p>This old Japanese-style house is so full of character. It features shutters with a slight Western-style. When I asked, I found out that the house was built in the 1930s, when Japanese buildings built around that time incorporated many Western stylistic elements.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4039" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-3362603416_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4039" border="0" /></p>
<p>The sunlight shining over the roof. The old house, the greenery and the faint yellow light shining out of the windows look like a scene taken straight from a classic film from the golden age of cinema.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4022" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-1600769233_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4022" border="0" /></p>
<p>Seeing the dense trees "growing" out of the roof of the house, you would never think you are in one of the busiest areas of Taipei.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4044" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-573139635_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4044" border="0" /></p>
<p>I love walking around the house. I particularly like turning corners to appreciate the architecture. I especially get a feeling of anticipation the moment just before I turn a corner.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4035" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-2103100625_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4035" border="0" /></p>
<p>Hand-painted fans hanging on the wall. The subdued color of the wood really brings out the beauty of the fans.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4033" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-3242388792_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4033" border="0" /></p>
<p>As soon as you go through the front door, you will see the '366 Birthday Flowers' wall on the right-hand side. It showcases the flowers of Taiwan which correspond with the days of the year.</p>
<p>The unique symbols represent the characteristics of each flower. Your can then ask an astrologer to match the characteristics of a flower with the personality for your date of birth.</p>
<p>My friend said that she wanted to find the symbol for her date of birth and use it as inspiration for a tattoo. (Pretty cool.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4026" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-3228386311_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4026" border="0" /></p>
<p>There is also a small shop inside that sells things featuring the 366 birthday flowers.</p>
<p>Creativity has been used to bring the past to life in modern design. This is quite fashionable lately.</p>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4019" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-3442066675_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4019" border="0" /></p>
<p>When I looked up, I saw a cute little second floor. I suddenly thought how nice it would be to live here.</p>
<p>I would love to stay in such a unique house surrounded by greenery. I wonder if they will ever turn this place into a guesthouse (heh heh, I can always hope).</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4052" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-1307610048_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4052" border="0" /></p>
<p>I really like this window lattice. They are not very regular in shape but look quite orderly. It is like a work of art.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4028" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-3815724353_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4028" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>The roof features traditional Taiwanese-style tiles, Japanese-style eaves, and a special green color... I really admire the architect's sense of aesthetics.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="青田七六" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-1963821848_n.jpg" alt="青田七六" border="0" /></p>
<p>The whole building is adorned with greenery.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4025" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-1334161636_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4025" border="0" /></p>
<p>There is also a small pond. There was duckweed, and small goldfish were swimming in the water. It was so pleasant. Just looking at this pond makes you feel so laid-back and relaxed.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4031" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349879303-2031725780_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4031" border="0" /></p>
<p>At the back of the main house is a semi-outdoor café. The eaves and the special design extend to the wooden skylight curtains.</p>
<p>It was a fascinating fusion of the old and the new.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4016" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-1249992151_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4016" border="0" /></p>
<p>The romantic European-style wall lights contrasting with the mottled wooden planks beautifully convey the history of the building.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4055" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-1541333018_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4055" border="0" /></p>
<p>A very characterful corner of the garden.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4056" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-2918344640_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4056" border="0" /></p>
<p>The window frames, rattan chairs and tables are all made of wood but have different textures, creating multi-layered aesthetics.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4058" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-1332658021_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4058" border="0" /></p>
<p>I always like to chill out when I am taking a break from work. It will be amazing to sit on this windowsill and relax.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4057" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-2245271207_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4057" border="0" /></p>
<p>It will be great to sit here and enjoy a good meal. (Too bad we did not have time to order any food during this visit. What a pity. ...)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4018" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-3587346713_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4018" border="0" /></p>
<p>The skylights above let in dazzling rays of sunlight. Spectacular.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img title="IMG_4017" src="../../images/article/myself/selected03/1349881648-2648254463_n.jpg" alt="IMG_4017" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;The menu on the wall is designed just like at a Japanese bar.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Qingtian Geo 76: Reflections</strong></p>
<p>The promotion and preservation of history are the main goals of Qingtian Geo 76. Such devotion to preservation and dedication to creativity has made this wondrous place surrounded by culture and greenery available to everyone in Taipei, a city in which the pace of life is becoming increasingly hectic.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Why not drop by to relax for an hour or two? Open your eyes, ears and come to Qingtian Street for a visit to Qingtian Geo 76. Take a deep breath and inhale the phytoncides given off by the plants, and appreciate the efforts of phytoncides to preserve this old architectural site.</p>
<p>................................................................................................................................</p>
<p><strong>Heritage & Geosciences</strong>&nbsp; <a href="http://www.geo76.tw" target="_blank">www.geo76.tw</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tour booking: (02)2700-0693 (tours must be booked in advance)<br />Café reservations: (02)2391-6676 opening hours: 11:30~21:00；9:00~21:00(Saturdays and Sundays)</p>
<p>Closed every Monday.</p>
<div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">Closed every Monday.
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address: 
            
            </td>
                <td>No. 6, Lane 7, Qingtian Street, Daan District, Taipei</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Telephone: </td>
                <td>02-2391-6676</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Getting there: </td>
                <td>Taipei Metro Guting station exit 5.Walk along Heping East Road for 10 minutes, turn left onto Qingtian Street, and then turn right at Lane 7. It is on the right.</td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>
        </div>
          ]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>4</subjectid>
      <region>1</region>
	  <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/480?category=myself</link>
    </article>
    <article>
      <folder>/images/article/reminiscent/selected05/</folder>
      <title>Nanzhuang and Guihua Lane: A Journey Back in Time!</title>
      <subtitle>The retro cinema and little shops brought childhood memories flooding back...<br />
	  Arriving in Nanzhuang was like stepping back to the good old days through a time warp.
</subtitle>
      <author>達人：Aiko</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[<p>I've always loved the retro feel of Nanzhuang, and today I decided to go for a day trip down the memory lane. We parked next to Nanzhuang Cinema. As soon as we got out of the car, we saw the retro movie posters and the showtimes of old movies! Old posters always carry wonderful memories, like the bicycles used to promote movies and the little shops in front of the cinema. Nowadays we have popcorn and soda... What was fashionable back then is what people now call "retro"... How times change!</p>

  <img src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected05/reminiscent_bigpic.jpg" width="626" height="276" class="selected_pic" />
<br />
<p>
<img src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected05/reminiscent_pic1.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected05/reminiscent_pic2.jpg" />
</p><br  />
<h3 style=" color:#e58a01">Nanzhuang Cinema</h3>
No. 55, Lane 3, Zhongshan Rd, Si Village, Nanzhuang Township, Miaoli County
<p>After leaving Nanzhuang Cinema, we simply had to go to Guihua Lane – the liveliest area in Nanzhuang! At the entrance to the lane were lots of direction signs, and you could also hear the rumbling of flowing water. The entrance to Guihua Lane was actually a public laundry basin! Thick stone slabs were placed above a basin, and the local residents once used the bumpy surfaces of these slabs to wash their clothes as they chatted to each other. Life was simple then!</p>
<p>Today there was an old lady washing clothes with a bar of crystal soap. But later I saw a stall-keeper flick his cigarette butt into the basin. The water was constantly flowing, but I couldn't help thinking of all the cigarette ash... When I saw him throw his cigarette butt in there, I thought how dirty the basin must be. But when I took a look inside, it was actually so clear that I could see the bottom! Maybe it's because the water was flowing all the time.</p>
<p>People used to live in poverty and had only a few possessions. They were very smart to build this public laundry basin. Not only did it provide a facility for everyone to conveniently wash their clothes, but doing laundry together also gave people a chance to chat. On the one hand, they could be distracted from the pain caused by such hard work. On the other hand, they could also make emotional connections through chatting. It just goes to show how friendly a place Taiwan is!</p>
<img src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected05/reminiscent_bigpic2.jpg" width="626" height="241" style="margin-bottom:10px;"/ >

<h3 style=" color:#e58a01">Shuibiantou Laundry Basin</h3>
East Entrance to Guihua Lane, Nanzhuang Township, Miaoli County
<br/><br  />
<img src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected05/reminiscent_pic3.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected05/reminiscent_pic4.jpg" /><p>We filled up on snacks along Guihua Lane. When we emerged, we saw an old post office. The post office is no longer in use and is now just a sightseeing spot. You could still picture it in its heyday; it's almost completely made of wood and adopted the Japanese style. I loved it ^^. Other than the nostalgic environment, all around Miaoli you could see traditional floral cloth and old posts remaining from Japanese-style buildings. I wondered how precise the calculations must have been to use wooden posts like those to support an entire house. When we saw these, KJ and me were amazed...</p><br />
<h3 style=" color:#e58a01">The Old Nanzhuang Post Office</h3>
No. 5, Wenhua Rd, Dong Village, Nanzhuang Township, Miaoli County
<p>Just as we were about to leave Nanzhuang, we saw a building with old-fashioned wooden windows and retro terrazzo flooring that could have been the set for a TV show 20 years ago... It turned out to be the back of the Miaoli Bus Station and it is still in use! Nanzhuang was really small but full of surprises. Arriving in Nanzhuang was like stepping back to the good old days through a time warp.</p>

    </div>
    
        <div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
               <span class="position-name">Nanzhuang Cinema</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
  <tr>
    <td class="item">
Address：

</td>
    <td>No. 55, Lane 3, Zhongshan Rd, Si Village, Nanzhuang Township, Miaoli County</td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Transportation：</td>
    <td>National Highway 1 → Toufen Interchange → Sanwan Exit → Provincial Highway 3 and County Route 124 for Sanwan → Pass Sanwan Junior High School
	<br />
	At Sanwan Bridge, turn left onto Miaoli Route 20 → Longmenkou Tunnel → You will arrive at the old streets of Nanzhuang in 5 minutes.
<br />
  Public transportation: Take the Mountain Line train to Toufen Township, Miaoli County and then take the Hsinchu Bus service to Nanzhuang.</td>
  </tr>
</table>       
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>5</subjectid>
      <region>3</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/0?category=reminiscent</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/reminiscent/selected02/</folder>
      <title>Hualien: A Warm and Pleasant Time at Time Second-Hand Bookshop</title>
      <subtitle>
        I'm so glad there is such a little corner in Taiwan brimming with culture and feeling. I hope that everyone who visits Hualien takes a stroll through Time.
      </subtitle>
      <author>Bonita</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[
          <p><img title="64" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391311-2951690854_n.jpg" alt="64" border="0" /></p>
<p>As I was organizing my photos half way through writing up my trip through the Kansai region, I discovered that I still hadn't written up a trip that I took in Taiwan several months ago, so I'm making my entry today. This was a short spring trip with my friend this April. We spent two days and one night in Hualien, where we enjoyed a comfortable stay at the new Fullon Hotel. It was the first time I'd ever ridden the Taroko Express! Before setting off, I took the time to research for some places that should not be missed as well as some others recommended by friends. 'Time' was amongst these.</p>
<p><img title="65" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391319-2263367950_n.jpg" alt="65" border="0" /></p>
<p>Time is located in a small alleyway but is not difficult to find because the famous Scallion Pancake street is nearby. It's also because of this that Time has 'No eating scallion pancakes in store' written on its wood-framed windows.</p>
<p><img title="66" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391326-1070822911_n.jpg" alt="66" border="0" /></p>
<p>I fell in love with the place as soon as I turned into the alleyway. The yellow walls, blue window frames and slender wooden slats offered a glimpse of the yellow light inside. They all combined to create a warm and cozy atmosphere that invited us in to look around.</p>
<p><img title="68" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391338-2061860911_n.jpg" alt="68" border="0" /></p>
<p>When we opened the door, we saw a vast array handmade items on display. It's not only a second-hand bookshop. They sell all sorts of other interesting things as well.</p>
<p><img title="67" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391332-3631226905_n.jpg" alt="67" border="0" />&nbsp; <br />
  <img title="69" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391343-11556739_n.jpg" alt="69" border="0" /> <br />
  <img title="70" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391349-3852485989_n.jpg" alt="70" border="0" /></p>
<p>
  <img title="73" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391366-2534574433_n.jpg" alt="73" border="0" /></p>
<p>Time has lots of hand-carved wooden seals; I opened up my TN straight away and stamped an entire page. Don't forget to bring your notebook if you visit!</p>
<p><img title="71" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391354-163470717_n.jpg" alt="71" border="0" /></p>
<p>There were also wooden racks containing lots of pamphlets about caring for stray animals. The owner must be a really compassionate person (The Time blog also has lots of information about stray animals!).</p>
<p>&nbsp;<img title="72" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391359-3037697067_n.jpg" alt="72" border="0" /></p>
<p><img title="75" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391378-591412651_n.jpg" alt="75" border="0" /></p>
<p>There's something unique to be found in every corner of the shop.</p>
<p><img title="76" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391384-1351403357_n.jpg" alt="76" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <img title="77" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391391-2563208030_n.jpg" alt="77" border="0" /> <img title="78" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391397-819889860_n.jpg" alt="78" border="0" /></p>
<p>After walking further into the shop, we saw that there was also an area for children's books. As someone who was raised to be environmentally friendly, I was quite impressed. This kills two birds with one stone by conserving natural resources as well as conveying knowledge to the next generation!</p>
<p><img title="79" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391402-3199573949_n.jpg" alt="79" border="0" /></p>
<p>At the back of the shop was a little area that had been separated off. It's an ideal place for quiet reading. All you have to do is buy a drink and you can while away the time there with a good book.</p>
<p><img title="80" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391407-3628183692_n.jpg" alt="80" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp; <img title="81" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391412-779045670_n.jpg" alt="81" border="0" /> <img title="82" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391417-1212842397_n.jpg" alt="82" border="0" /> <img title="83" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391422-1191685340_n.jpg" alt="83" border="0" /> <img title="84" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391427-1351932121_n.jpg" alt="84" border="0" /> <img title="85" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391432-3606545442_n.jpg" alt="85" border="0" /></p>
<p>I was told there was also a small attic, but we didn't see it while we were there.</p>
<p><img title="86" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391436-1809341047_n.jpg" alt="86" border="0" />&nbsp;</p>
<p>I'm so glad I discovered this place and hope that I come to have many more warm places like this in my life. Hualien may not have Eslite but it has Time!</p>
<p>&nbsp;<img title="87" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391443-2281220816_n.jpg" alt="87" border="0" /> <img title="88" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391451-3761276777_n.jpg" alt="88" border="0" /> <img title="89" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391455-3063127908_n.jpg" alt="89" border="0" /></p>
<p><img title="74" src="../../images/article/reminiscent/selected02/1347391372-3729890050_n.jpg" alt="74" border="0" /></p>
<p>It's a definite must-visit if you ever find yourself in Hualien.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Opening hours: 13:00-22:00</p>
<p>Blog: <a href="http://blog.roodo.com/bookslight" target="_blank">http://blog.roodo.com/bookslight</a></p>
<div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG"><span class="store_name">Time Second-Hand Bookshop</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
  <tr>
    <td class="item">Address: </td>
    <td> 8 Jianguo Road, Hualien City, Hualien County</td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Telephone: </td>
    <td>03-8358312</td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td>Getting there: </td>
    <td> In the alley opposite the 7-Eleven next to the City Office</td>
  </tr>
</table>       
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>
        </div>
          ]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>5</subjectid>
      <region>2</region>
	  <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/441?category=reminiscent</link>
    </article>
    <article>
      <folder>/images/article/romantic/selected05/</folder>
      <title>A Romantic Getaway at E-DA World</title>
      <subtitle>E-DA World is an ideal destination for couples looking for a short getaway. If you don't have the time to go abroad, a trip to E-DA World is the next best thing.</subtitle>
      <author>By 莎莎</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[<p>I've always dreamed of a trip to Europe with Dadai. Even though this is not yet possible for us right now, we can still travel by the high-speed rail for two hours and get away from the hustle and bustle of Taipei to Kaohsiung's beautiful and picturesque E-DA Word – a place that makes you feel as if you've been transported to Europe.</p>
  <img src="../../images/article/romantic/selected05/romantic_bigpic.jpg" width="627" height="275" class="selected_pic" /><div class="selected_mark">
</div>

<p>With the romantic atmosphere of Europe, E-DA World is the perfect place to take a short two-day getaway and unwind. You can stay at the luxurious and romantic Crowne Plaza and enjoy its facilities, head for the outlet mall with international brands for a shopping spree, and have fun and excitement in the theme park with its ancient Greek ambiance. We were never short of something to do during our two-day and one-night stay, and the time was never enough. It was really fun!</p>
<p>To avoid the crowd, we decided to check in to Crowne Plaza on Sunday, go to E-DA Theme Park on Monday, and then take the high speed rail back to Taipei in the evening. Although that meant I had to take a day off work, we could pack in even more fun!</p>

<p>On the first day of our romantic getaway, we made our way to the shopping center. There were some great bargains to be discovered at the outlet shops, but the best thing had to be the design of the ceiling that looked like a romantic starry night sky. It made us feel like walking along one of the fashionable streets in Europe! The design is similar to that of the Venus Fort at Odaiba in Tokyo and The Venetian in Macao. You don't have to worry about getting sunburned or caught in the rain; you can simply enjoy a stroll under the blue sky. And now you can have such a romantic experience without even leaving the country!</p><p><img src="../../images/article/romantic/selected05/romantic_pic1.jpg"  /><img src="../../images/article/romantic/selected05/romantic_pic2.jpg" /></p>
<p>In the evening, we went back to the hotel to enjoy its facilities, including the fully-equipped leisure center and the outdoor swimming pool with spa and a water slide. Relaxing in the pool in a summer's evening meant we didn't have to worry about sunburn or heat; there weren't as many people, either. The soft moonlight just added to the romantic atmosphere. Another highlight of the evening was the Dream Lake show. We watched as the rhythm of the lights and fountains changed with the music. It's really hard to put into words how I felt!</p>
<p>On the second day, the only thing on my schedule was to spend the entire day with Dadai at the ancient Greece-themed E-DA Theme Park. Looking back, I hadn't been to such a large theme park for a really really long time. I shouted and screamed with joy just like a child. This was our first time to date in a theme park with Dadai, and it was to E-DA World filled with so much European ambiance. So romantic! E-DA Theme Park is the only theme park in Taiwan designed in the ancient Greek style. It's divided into the City of David, Santorini Mountain City, Trojan Castle and Ferris Wheel areas.</p>

<p>The magnificent David City had a large theater where you could watch performances at designated times. The Greek-style Santorini Mountain City really had a romantic Mediterranean atmosphere. The Trojan Castle was like something from the fairy tale: it's a huge castle with an imposing structure consisting of two levels under ground and four levels above ground, with rides on each level. The Ferris wheel was on the roof of the shopping center. When we entered the park, a member of staff stamped on our hands that passed to all the rides! Except for some large rides outside, most of the rides were indoors so we didn't have to endure queuing up under the baking hot sun. If it had rained, we wouldn't have got soaking wet.</p>
<img src="../../images/article/romantic/selected05/romantic_pic3.jpg" /><img src="../../images/article/romantic/selected05/romantic_pic4.jpg" />
<p>During our day at the theme park, we watched an excellent musical performance in City of David and took a relaxing stroll around Santorini Mountain City. It really felt like we were vacationing in the Mediterranean as we walked past the white, blue, yellow and green-colored buildings. It was like a dream. Even though the sun in southern Taiwan was scorching hot, I kept bugging Dadai to take pictures of me. He hated the sun and ended up sweating buckets.</p>
<p>We had such a great time having a go on all the rides on each level of the Trojan Castle. There was a carousel, bumper cars, a haunted house, Fly Over Taiwan, and lots more. Dadai didn't mind being shaken around, so he went on some crazy spinning rides by himself. Of the big rides, we only went on the pirate ship because all others looked so scary. I think I must be getting more cowardly as I get older; when I went to theme parks before, I wanted the rides to be as thrilling as possible. But now just looking at them at the bottom makes my heart race and my legs numb. Even so, standing safely on the ground and listening to the screams of the people above were also pretty fun, hahaha.</p>
<p>Our last stop before heading home was the roof of the shopping center to ride Taiwan's highest Ferris wheel. As the Ferris wheel gradually took us higher and higher, we got a panoramic view of the landscape surrounding E-DA World. When we reached the very top, the view was spectacular. We could see very far and it was breathtaking! Even though it was afternoon and the sun of southern Taiwan was still roasting hot, luckily the Ferris wheel had air conditioning. If you go there, remember to take sunglasses though, as the sun is still dazzling in the evening!</p>
<p>E-DA World is an ideal destination for couples looking for a short getaway. If you don't have the time to go abroad, a trip to E-DA World is the next best thing. This was our first time to date in a theme park with Dadai, and I'm so happy that it was to E-DA World. We have so many beautiful memories that will stay with us forever.</p>
<p>Over the two days and one night of our trip, we stayed comfortably, ate delicious food, shopped to our satisfaction, and had great fun. There was so much to enjoy. With all of our beautiful memories, we happily made our way back to Taipei. We couldn't have asked for more from our getaway to E-DA World! Our romantic trip also brought me and Dadai even closer together (blush).</p>

    </div>
    
        <div class="placeArea">
            <div class="placeBG">
                    <span class="position-name">E-DA World</span>
              <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
              <tr>
                <td class="item">
            Address：
            
            </td>
                <td>No. 12, Section 1, Xuecheng Road, Sanhe Village, Dashu District, Kaohsiung City</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Telephone：</td>
                <td>0800-656-077</td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>Transportation：</td>
                <td>Take the high-speed train to Zuoying Station; from THSR Zuoying Station exit 2, walk to bus station platform 5 and take the E-DA BUS 'HSR Zuoying' route.</td>
              </tr>
            </table>        
            </div>
            <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>6</subjectid>
      <region>4</region>
      <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/0?category=romantic</link>
    </article>
	<article>
      <folder>/images/article/romantic/selected04/</folder>
      <title>Jiaoxi.Culinary Delights: Stunning Handmade Cakes Madeleine Coffee Shop</title>
      <subtitle>
        The Madeleine Coffee Shop serves the highest quality delicacies while staying true to its unique local flavor. Why not come and partake of afternoon tea when you have time?
      </subtitle>
      <author>rechal63</author>
      <content>
        <![CDATA[
		<p><img title="_A050052-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349442885-3770646192.jpg" alt="_A050052-1" border="0" /> &nbsp;</p>
              <p>&nbsp;I heard that the owner's wife was inspired to name the coffee shop "Madeleine" after the madeleine cakes that she made when learning how to make French pâtisserie. The owner arrived in Jiaoxi 3 years ago to open the coffee shop. After talking to the owner, I gathered that they originally served only coffee but then taught themselves how to make cakes and biscuits to diversify their business. As everything is handmade, quantities are limited. If you are going to "Madelene" especially to eat desserts, make sure you have a reservation or call ahead to check whether they have what you want to taste!</p>
              <p><img title="_A050025" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349442921-391644736.jpg" alt="_A050025" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
              <p>The owner said that the business only started to pick up half a year ago. Things did not go well initially, and one of them had to go out to work in order to support their dream! It is due to the high standards and expectations they put on themselves that made their pastries have such appeal!</p>
              <p><img title="_A050026" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349442921-1727020714.jpg" alt="_A050026" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050028-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349442972-1849312334.jpg" alt="_A050028-1" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
              <p>The interior of the coffee shop is warm and comfortable.</p>
              <p><img title="_A050029-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349442972-1387984382.jpg" alt="_A050029-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p>The coffee shop has also been featured in Next Magazine!</p>
              <p><img title="_A050031" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443093-2781353439.jpg" alt="_A050031" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
              <p>Even though we did not make a reservation beforehand, we still managed to enjoy the café's famous cheesecake, honey madeleines, waffles, American coffee and lychee beer. Haha...That's right. Beer with afternoon tea. We must be a couple of alcoholics!</p>
              <p><img title="_A050034" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349451333-918993709.jpg" alt="_A050034" border="0" /> &nbsp;</p>
              <p>Madeleines are the epitome of French pâtisserie and have traditionally been regarded as a type of biscuits in France. Their most distinctive feature is the shell-like shape. When fresh out of the oven, the rim around the outside of the shell shape has a crispy texture, and the center is thick with a spongy cake-like texture. Its fragrance of honey and a delicate hint of lemon make it the ideal accompaniment to a cup of tea. (It was a shame we ordered beer instead.)</p>
              <p><img title="_A050033-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443148-1812345508.jpg" alt="_A050033-1" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
              <p>&nbsp;The Caffè Americano (60 NTD) is made using imported Italian coffee beans as opposed to home roasting coffee.  It had multiple levels of flavor and tasted amazing! I heard that the owner was highly skilled at latte art, so this place is definitely worth a visit for coffee fans.</p>
              <p><img title="_A050035-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443148-905106275.jpg" alt="_A050035-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p>Cheesecake: Ice-cold and delicate with a natural milk aroma and a cheesy taste that was just right. It was so creamy.</p>
              <p><img title="_A050039-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443148-1240298202.jpg" alt="_A050039-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050050" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443196-504373265.jpg" alt="_A050050" border="0" /> &nbsp;</p>
              <p>Honey waffles: The plate was decorated with a pattern drawn using chocolate sauce. It looked so delicious.</p>
              <p><img title="_A050047-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443196-1044265838.jpg" alt="_A050047-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050041" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443242-1006627529.jpg" alt="_A050041" border="0" /></p>
              <p>The <a title="http://www.wretch.cc/blog/usadvd/2976532" href="http://www.wretch.cc/blog/usadvd/2976532">lychee beer </a>we ordered tasted much better than the fruit beers which have been so popular this year! The scent of lychees filled our noses as soon as we poured it. It was so smooth and made us feel a little tipsy.</p>
              <p><img title="_A050059-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443242-3265979015.jpg" alt="_A050059-1" border="0" />&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
              <p><img title="_A050065" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443262-2550506797.jpg" alt="_A050065" border="0" /></p>
              <p>Sorry! I made a total mess cutting the waffle.</p>
              <p><img title="_A050066-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443289-2294093578.jpg" alt="_A050066-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050068-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443344-3370518786.jpg" alt="_A050068-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050073-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443344-190377592.jpg" alt="_A050073-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050075-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443440-3394152955.jpg" alt="_A050075-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050076-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443440-3465948951.jpg" alt="_A050076-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p><img title="_A050079-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443440-3351096026.jpg" alt="_A050079-1" border="0" /> &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
              <p>This is the friendly owner. He will do his best to answer all your questions.</p>
              <p>I hope I can eat different cakes next time I visit!</p>
              <p><img title="_A050077-1" src="../../images/article/romantic/selected04/1349443440-2371748031.jpg" alt="_A050077-1" border="0" /></p>
              <p>Some of the Treats Offered:</p>
              <p><strong>Banana chiffon cake:</strong> Japanese chiffon cake is very popular due to its light, delicate texture and simple ingredients. It is made using fresh eggs, high-quality flour, sugar and olive oil. Fresh banana, pumpkin or other ingredients are then added to this mixture before baking!</p>
              <p><strong>Chiffon cake:</strong>Made using 100% pure olive oil and high-quality flour comparable with that from Japan and France. Adding organic muesli from the banks of the river Rhine in Germany and rum raisins accentuates the cake's delicate texture while giving the crunch taste of fresh muesli.</p>
              <p><strong>Quiche:</strong> Even though it is salty, it is an excellent accompaniment to black coffee.</p>
              <p>&nbsp;</p>
              <p>Coffee Shop Information</p>
              <p>Address:<a class="smaplink" title="Map" > 86 Deyang Road, Jiaoxi Township, Yilan County</a>[<a href="http://www.ete.com.tw/springhotel/location.htm">(next to Chunhe Japanese-style Outdoor Hot Spring)</a>]&nbsp;<br />
                Telephone: 03-9873173<br />
                Opening hours: Sunday–Thursday (11:00–23:00), Friday and Saturday (11:00–24:00)<br />
                Closed: Tuesday<br />
                <strong><span style="color: #407f00;">Closed: Tuesday </span></strong><a href="http://madeleine.mmmtravel.com.tw/">http://madeleine.mmmtravel.com.tw/</a></p>
				<div class="placeArea">
              <div class="placeBG"><span class="store_name">Madeleine Coffee Shop
                <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
                  <tr>
                    <td class="item"> Address:  </td>
                    <td>86 Deyang Road, Jiaoxi Township, Yilan County</td>
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td>Telephone: </td>
                    <td>03-9873173</td>
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td>Telephone: </td>
                    <td>National Highway 5 route  
                      1: Head for Toucheng Interchange in the direction from Taipei to Yilan >> turn left onto Section 1, Qingyun Road >> proceed to Section 7, Jiaoxi Road >> Section 5, Jiaoxi Road >> turn right at 85°C >> ascend the hill for approximately 500 m >> turn left and proceed for approximately 800 m >> the café is on the right-hand side, opposite the hot springs park. <br />
                      2: Head for Toucheng Interchange in the direction from Yilan to Taipei >> turn left onto Section 1, Qingyun Road >> proceed to Section 7, Jiaoxi Road >> Section 5, Jiaoxi Road >> turn right at 85°C >> ascend the hill for approximately 500 m >> turn left and proceed for approximately 800 m >> the café is on the right-hand side, opposite the hot springs park. </td>
                  </tr>
                </table>
              </span></div>
              <span class="store_name">
                <div class="placeBox">&nbsp;</div>
              </span></div>
		]]>
      </content>
      <subjectid>6</subjectid>
      <region>2</region>
	  <selected>1</selected>
      <link>http://win888.events.pixnet.net/articles/430?category=romantic</link>
    </article>
  </articles>

  <subjects>
    <subject key="economy" name="Youth for Good Value" descript="Enjoy breathtaking scenery and great delicacies at low prices! Introduce affordable (or free) attractions and food in Taiwan." />
    <subject key="family" name="Youth for Family" descript="Youth is a leaf in a tree of life, from which stems all the family members. Introduce attractions and restaurants in Taiwan suitable for family reunions." />
    <subject key="luxury" name="Youth for Luxury" descript="Indulge in sheer sensual enjoyment! Introduce luxurious attractions and restaurants in Taiwan." />
    <subject key="myself" name="Youth for Daydreaming" descript="Youth is like a secret diary. Introduce attractions and restaurants in Taiwan suitable for woolgathering, daydreaming, and looking for oneself." />
    <subject key="reminiscent" name="Youth for Nostalgia" descript="With the heart of a youth, let’s go back to the future through the past. Introduce historical stores, sites, buildings or refreshments in Taiwan." />
    <subject key="romantic" name="Youth for Romance" descript="Why do you need a reason to fall in love? Introduce  attractions and restaurants in Taiwan suitable for dating and marriage proposals." />
  </subjects>

  <regions>
    <a_region>Northern Taiwan</a_region>
    <a_region>Eastern Taiwan</a_region>
    <a_region>Central Taiwan</a_region>
    <a_region>Southern Taiwan</a_region>
    <a_region>Outlying Islands</a_region>
    <a_region>Featured Articles</a_region>
    <a_region>Favorites</a_region>
  </regions>

</data>